我想通过与你分享他们两个非常棒的研究视频来结束
I'd like to finish off by sharing with you two quite amazing research videos they both
展示组合从多个视点获取的视觉信息的力量。
show the power of combining visual information taken from multiple viewpoints.
第一个是绘制大型照片库的系统，例如Flickr。在这
The first is a system that draws large repositories of photographs, for instance, Flickr. In this
他们检索了大量罗马的照片。
case they retrieve a whole lot of images taken of Rome.
不同人在不同时间拍摄的所有这些图像显然都有很多重叠。
All of these images taken by different people at different times clearly have a lot of overlap.
他们所做的是在多个图像中找到相同的点，然后是它们
What they do is they find the same points in multiple images and from that then, they
然后可以重建拍摄这些照片的相机的相对精度。
can then reconstruct the relative precision of the cameras that took those pictures.
然后他们可以将这些信息组合成数百甚至数千张图片
Then they can combine this information across hundreds or even thousands of pictures and
用它来重建一个完整的三维模型。
use that to reconstruct a full three-dimensional model.
他们没有去参观，他们只是在网上挖掘已有的照片
They didn't have to go and visit, they just mined the web for photographs that were already
在那里，有一些非常聪明的算法能够从所有这些图片中提取，
there, and with some very clever algorithms were able to extract from all those pictures,
这个三维模型。
this three dimensional model.
下一个扩展了该技术，以组合数以百万计的信息
This next one extends the technique to combine information from millions and millions of
不同的人用不同的相机拍摄的图像在不同的时间但是相同的主题。
images taken by different people with different cameras at different times but of the same subject matter.